<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MixTape</string>
    <string name="createNewMixtape">+ Create New Mixtape</string>
    <string name="workoutMix">Workout Mix</string>
    <string name="workoutMixtime">Time: 45:37</string>
    <string name="studyMix">Study Mix</string>
    <string name="studyMixTime">Time: 1:01:10</string>
    <string name="roadtripMix">Roadtrip 1995 mix</string>
    <string name="roadtripMixTime">Time: 39:42</string>
    <string name="degrassi">I Love Degrassi!</string>
    <string name="degrassiTime">Time: 23:33</string>
    <string name="track1">Track 1</string>
    <string name="track2">Track 2</string>
    <string name="track3">Track 3</string>
    <string name="addTrack">+ Add Track</string>
    <string name="mainScreen">
        This is the main screen\n
        This is the first screen the user sees when they start the app\n
        This screen shows what mixtapes (playlists)  are available to them\n
        From here the user can either create a new mixtape,\n
        or play a mixtape created by themselves or a friend\n
        The technical hurdles will be to share mixtapes amoung friends.\n
        This would require all data to be in a cloud database.
    </string>
    <string name="createMixtape">
        The screen is for creating new mixtapes\n
        Each mixtape is a series of music tracks\n
        This screen will start looking empty\n
        Ths user needs to add tracks\n
        After the track is added, this view will show the\n
        song name, artist name, album name, a button to preview the song\n
        A link to share the mixtape with a friend or group of friends. \n
        This screen will keep a running total of time, let the user order the tracks\n
        From here the user can press the Add Track button\n
        and go to the search screen to find tracks to add.
    </string>
    <string name="searchTracks">
        The search tracks screen is for searching for tracks to add.\n
        Technical hurldes would be a way to sort cloud based music\n
        A search bar to find Artists, genres, similar music etc.\n
        A list of available tracks would be below the search bar.

    </string>
    <string name="nowPlaying">
        Now playing will show the cover art on top with controls such as play\\pause\\next track\n
        Below the control buttons will be the track list that will link\n
        to a page that will give more information about the artist, \n
        as well as give suggestions for similar tracks.\n
        I don\'t know all the technical hurles,\n
        but I think owning the license to the music would be one.
        
    </string>
    <string name="trackInformation">
        This view gives a user information about\n
        the song/album/artist etc.\n
        Then show the user similar songs/artists that are available.\n
        The tecnical challeges here would be to get the information from some library.

    </string>
</resources>
